{
    "subject": "resource/Johann_Karl_Burckhardt",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Johann Karl Burckhardt",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Johann Karl Burckhardt is Johann Karl Burckhardt.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9874454736709595,
            "question": "What is the full name of Johann Karl Burckhardt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9874215126037598,
            "question": "Is 'Johann Karl' part of Johann Karl Burckhardt's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9762858152389526,
            "question": "What is the structure of Johann Karl Burckhardt's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9673582911491394,
            "question": "Is Johann Karl Burckhardt's first name Johann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9655746221542358,
            "question": "If Johann Karl Burckhardt's full name is given, what is his first name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9579062461853027,
            "question": "Does Johann Karl Burckhardt have a middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9529502987861633,
            "question": "What are the two parts of Johann Karl Burckhardt's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9486897587776184,
            "question": "Does Johann Karl Burckhardt have a single name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9216720461845398,
            "question": "What is the second part of Johann Karl Burckhardt's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9142079949378967,
            "question": "Is Johann Karl a person's full name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Johann Karl Burckhardt is Johann Karl Burckhardt.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4558_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the second part of Johann Karl Burckhardt's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4558_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Johann Karl Burckhardt have a single name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4558_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the two parts of Johann Karl Burckhardt's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4558_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4558_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention two individuals with similar names, but different full names and dates of birth/death:\n\n* Johann Karl Burckhardt (1773-1825) was a German-born astronomer and mathematician.\n* Jacob Christoph Burckhardt (1818-1897) was a Swiss cultural historian.\n\nTherefore, it is not accurate to say that the full name of Johann Karl Burckhardt is simply \"Johann Karl Burckhardt\", as there are different individuals with this name."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that confirms Johann Karl Burckhardt's full name as Johann Karl Burckhardt."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information suggests that Johann Karl Burckhardt adopted the name Jean Charles Burckhardt when he became a naturalized French citizen, implying that his full name was indeed Johann Karl Burckhardt.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}